

Antoine Le Bras

Product designer

Phone: (+33) 6 52 43 69 67 Email: antoine.lebras1@gmail.com Portfolio: antoine-lebras.store

As a UX enthusiast, I love solving people's real problems by addressing them via useful, enjoyable, and intuitive user experiences. It gives me a sense of satisfaction to know that I can make a difference in users' daily lives.

Work experience

Andjaro - Product designer

Apprenticeship Paris Sept 2021 - Sept 2023

- Worked with all stakeholders of a product team and developers. Responsible for the user experience of the mobile site as lead designer on the redesign as well as the creation of the registration tunnel.
- Worked around all the planning elements present on Andjaro (SaaS platform and mobile site): team planning, individual and personal planning.

Slumberland - UX/UI designer

Internship Paris Mar 2021 - Sept 2021

- Participation in a long term project for Dassaut Falcon: from the creation of wireframes and mock-ups, the initialization of a design system to usability tests.
- Creation of wireframes and mock-ups for the Société Générale group adapted to the Typo 3 CMS.
- Creation of a hearing loss simulator and flyer customization tool for Sonance Audition.

DataGrowb' - UI designer

Internship Nantes Mai 2020 - Jul 2020

Creation of the mistercoocky.com website from the design to the development.

My touch

I enjoy traveling abroad to experience new cultures and learn more about different ways of life. It helps me gain a broader perspective on the world around me and how I plan to influence it through my work.

On top of that, I am passionate about sports and e-sports, and am constantly on the lookout for the latest news in these fields. This allows me

to stay connected to what's going on in the world in areas I love

Education

ECV Digital - Master's degree in UX design

Paris 2021 to 2023

ECV Digital - Bachelor in digital project management

Nantes 2018 to 2021

Skills

UX-UI

Users interviews
Information architecture
Wireframing
Accessibility
Prototyping
Usability testing
Figma and Adobe tools

Langage

French native
English (TOEIC 825 - 2023)
HTML - CSS - JS

Soft skills

Critical look
Global vision on a product
Empathy
Pedagogy
Team player